D.C. Civil War Centennial Commission
DC Public Library, Special Collections
D.C. Civil War Centennial Commission Papers
1959-1966
DC Public Library, Special Collections
3 linear feet; 3 boxes
007
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1959-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ephemera invitations to events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ephemera programs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ephemera miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of centennial events of Paul Sedgwick, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of centennial events, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of centennial events awarding of centennial medals, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of centennial events awarding of centennial medals, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of centennial events, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of centennial events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of centennial events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs of centennial events, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of centennial events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of miscellaneous events, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Historic photographs used in the commemoration from forts, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Historic photographs for commemorations from the Library of Congress, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Historic photographs for commemorations from the U.S. Navy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Historic photographs for commemorations from the Brady Collection and U.S. Signal Corps, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Materials from mounted exhibits, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Programs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Press releases and publicity, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Takoma Park: 75 Year of Community Living, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Album loose-leaf pages, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Marcus T. Wright - Battles and Commanders of the Civil War, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 6)